I've actually seen Gina McKee in real life once before, about 15 years ago.
On the YouTube, there were only three of us in the carriage.
I whisper urgently, yet extremely quietly, to my 10-cent husband that Gina McKee, and
he boomed out in this huge man voice that is not Jillian McKee.
The gulf of a smile crossed her face, which was otherwise averted in palpable desire.
Not to get drawn in, so drew three conclusions, one of which I knew already, this actor has
an exquisitely readable face.
Her eyes can throw out a hundred distinct emotions a second.
She doesn't like the limelight, not at all, and I bet she's nice, happy to report having
met her properly on a hotel rooftop in London that I have once again completed right.